Olga Komarova:

student in web development

tel +45 424 11 088 okomaro@gmail.com www.komar.dk

Goal of this CV

I am a beginner in web-development and a 3rd semester student in multimedia design (front-end specialisation).

Currently, I am looking for an **internship** in a company located in **Copenhagen** with a focus on **web and mobile development and design,** starting from January 2019 fro min 3 months or longer.

I have 1,5 year experience in using HTML, CSS, SASS pre-processor, Bootstrap library, JavaScript, Angular framework, PHP and mySQL, as well as Wordpress CMS. I am very interested in UX/UI design.

Link to a projects portfolio www.komar.dk

Link to a student portfolio http://okomaro.bplaced.net/Portfolio_2_1/

Education

Student at CPH Business Academy, Lyngby Multimedia Design and frontend development (2017-2019), AP

Bachelor degree in International Business Belarusian State Economic University, faculty of International Economic Relations (1995-2000)

Languages

Danish – fluent, English – fluent, German – basic, Russian – native

Personal

Born in Belarus in 1978, live in Denmark since 2011. Optimistic, responsible, diligent and smart person. ESTP-A personality. I like to learn new things and enjoy interesting challenges in life. My hobbies are meditation, yoga, travelling, and reading. Married, child-free.

Work experience

My previous work experience lays in business administration, marketing, advertising and project-management. In August 2017 I have decided to invest time and effort to pursue my dream to use my interest to technologies and learn to program.

Thus my future employee will get a motivated tech specialist with experience in business processes and project-management.

Portfolio link: www.komar.dk CV updated 12.11.2018

Work experience in details:

Visas and Legalisations handling officer

Consular services agency, Comet Consular Services A/S (www.cometconsular.com) Copenhagen, Denmark

September 2013 until now

Responsibilities:

- establish and maintain cooperation with embassies/consulates and other authorities
- handling visa applications and legalisation of documents through the embassies in Copenhagen
- giving update on ongoing cases to clients via email, telephone and in person
- keeping updated the company's information database on the daily basis
- daily accounting of expenses in connection with the document flow

Head of the office

Russian visa application center, Invisa Fiduciary Services Aps (<u>www.ifs-denmark.com</u>), Copenhagen, Denmark

August 2012 - July 2013

Responsibilities:

- overall management of the office and its daily procedures
- establishing the procedures in connection with the applications for Russian visas
- · contacting the Russian consulate on the daily basis
- personnel management
- financial and overall reporting

Head of the subsidiary with the overall responsibility for leading the department

Internet advertising sales-house, RG Media (<u>www.rgmedia.by</u> , <u>www.redgraphic.com</u>), Minsk, Belarus

March 2009 - May 2010

Responsibilities:

- working out and adopting the yearly financial plan of the subsidiary
- negotiating and establishing partnerships with partners
- setting up sales targets, creating price lists, discount grids and drafts of agreements with customers and partners
- reporting to the company's owner on turnover statements and results
- hiring and managing of personnel, freelancers and maintenance assistants

Country sales representative (Russia, Ukraine, Belarus)

Spanish cheese manufacturers association Quorum International (www.quoruminter.com), Moscow, Russia

March 2007 - December 2008

Responsibilities

- establishing partnership with food importers and distributors of the diary products
- representing the association at exhibitions and Spanish trade chamber events
- translating and creating promotional materials and presentations
- assisting in negotiations between the association customers in Russia, Ukraine and Belarus

Portfolio link: www.komar.dk CV updated 12.11.2018

Head of advertising and PR division

International holding of transport and logistic companies
AsstrA Associated Traffic AG
(www.asstra.com), Moscow, Russia /
Minsk, Belarus
April 2002 - March 2007

Responsibilities

- creating, adopting and controlling of advertising and PR plans for overall activity on company's markets (Russia, Ukraine, Belarus, Lithuania, Poland, Germany, Italy, Switzerland, Kazakhstan, China)
- managing the division of advertising and PR (3 people) and coordinating the network of the sales managers (8 people) in local offices responsible for local marketing
- establishing and developing partnerships with subcontractors in all the markets
- participating in marketing strategy development and ISO 9001:2000 certification

Business development assistant

financial information agency Ecopress Ltd.(www.ecopress.by), Minsk, Belarus

February 2001 – March 2002

Responsibilities

- project management and promotion of the Belarusian news and search portal
- translation of news and documents for clients
- creating and running the new division for headhunting services within the company's activities – from business plan to sales

Other activities

From January 2009 til present: organizer and tour-leader of the yearly 3-week tour on the Trans-Siberian railroad for about 300 international participants with cultural and tourist program in the major Russian cities (www.lovingrussia.org).

Portfolio link: www.komar.dk CV updated 12.11.2018